Let's return to the 'Did you feel it?' app for a moment.
让我们暂且回到 "Did you feel it?" 应用
When we last left off, we observed that the app was crashing on launch
上次我们观察到 该应用会由于一个
because of a network on main threat exception.
NetworkOnMainThread 异常 在启动时崩溃
&gt;&gt; Yeah, Android doesn't allow developers to do network requests on
是的 Android 不允许 开发人员在主线程上
the main thread, because this will make our apps unresponsive and laggy.
进行网络请求 因为这会造成应用无响应和延迟
&gt;&gt; By throwing an exception that causes our apps to crash,
通过抛出一个异常 使应用崩溃
this forces developers to follow best practices and run networking code on
可以强制开发人员 使用最优的方法
the background thread and then return the results to the UI thread.
并且在后台线程上运行网络代码 然后将结果返回给 UI 线程
&gt;&gt; Yeah, so know that creating threads, coordinating work between them, and
没错 所以在计算机科学中 理解创建线程
communicating the results back and
协调线程之间的工作
forth is one of the hardest problems in computer science.
以及将结果来回传递 是最难的问题之一
&gt;&gt; In our case, we really don't need the full power of threading.
对我们来说 我们根本不需要线程的全部功能
All we want to do is run a single task, which is our HTTP request,
我们只需要在一个单独的线程上 运行一个任务 也就是 HTTP 请求
on a separate thread from the one that's handling events on our UI thread.
该线程不能是 用于处理我们的 UI 线程事件的线程
&gt;&gt; Yes, so Android framework engineers anticipated that this would be a common
是的 因此 Android 框架工程师 预料到这会变成
need and
一个普遍需求
created a specific Java class that makes this exact pattern really easy.
并创建了专门的 Java 类 使这一模式变得非常简单
It's called AsyncTask.
这个类叫做 AsyncTask
&gt;&gt; Async is short for
Async 是异步 (asynchronous) 的缩写
asynchronous which means that things can happen at different times.
意思是 事物可以在不同的时间进行
For example,
例如
the video you're watching right now is an example of an asynchronous learning.
你现在正在观看的视频 就是异步学习的一个示例
You don't have to be in a lecture hall at a particular time to watch it.
你不需要在特定时间 坐在教室里来看视频
AsyncTask is great for spurning a short lift one off task
AsyncTask 适合于 短期的一次性任务
without the overhead of managing a standard job thread.
避免管理标准作业线程 所需要的开销
&gt;&gt; It is not perfect for every threading situation,
它不能完美适用于 所有的线程情况
however, if you run into a situation where you need threads that exist for
但是如果需要使用 仅存在几秒钟的线程
more than a few seconds, you'll need to use something more robust.
就需要使用 更加可靠的方式
&gt;&gt; Yeah, so be sure to check out the Android Performance Pattern
没错 因此请务必观看一下关于线程的 “Android 性能模式”视频系列
video series on threading, linked below for more information.
下面的链接 提供了详细的信息
&gt;&gt; Anyway, since we don't want the UI for our app to freeze up for
既然我们不希望 应用从 Internet 检索数据时
a couple of seconds while the app retrieves some data from the Internet,
UI 会卡住几秒钟 那么 AsyncTask
AsyncTask is a perfect fit for this part of our app.
对于应用的这一部分来说 是非常合适的
&gt;&gt; Let's look at this in more detail.
让我们详细地了解一下吧
AsyncTask provide a way for us to easily hand off work to a background thread and
AsyncTask 提供了一种方式 可以简单地将作业转到后台线程
then receive the result whenever its done so we can update the UI.
并且在作业完成时随时接收到结果 用于更新 UI
Note that only a small amount of time will be take up on the main thread to
请注意 主线程接收到结果并更新 UI
actually get the result and update UI.
只需要很少的时间
So after work is completed, we no longer need the background thread anymore.
因此作业完成后 我们就不再需要该后台线程了